I know that the concept of pattern recognition is new for a lot of folks, but for those of us
who have it, it's not. It's like, oh, I see this, I see this, so this is what's going to happen.
And let me just tell you, the United States is not going to exist much longer. And I don't just
know that because of pattern recognition. I know that because I've dated a lot of United States
ass mofos. What I mean is individuals who are in a constant scramble to assert power that they
don't actually have grounded in anything substantive. They're always grasping at
straws. They're always changing who they're in alignment with. They're always shifting to
shifting blame and never taking accountability. And so they never actually get real footing.
And if you learn the history of this place, you know that it's never had real footing ever.
It's always in a scramble. It's always trying to blame somebody or deflect or do some type of
parapsychological manipulation to simply just avoid taking accountability for errors that it has made.
Because it's narcissism does not allow it to acknowledge its own errors.
I think the problem with so many of us here in the United States is a failure to acknowledge that
a society is comprised of humans with brains. And brains are susceptible to so much negativity,
egoism, and harm. And we look at this nation as if it is something on paper. We don't look at it as
something born from the minds of people. And the people it was born from were deeply flawed.
So the nation itself is deeply flawed. And if we don't actively start looking at what this place is
from that point of view, we can argue ourselves to death. We're never going to know what we're trying
to solve. Which is why the consistent effort to make the problem of the United States an issue of
election cycles is a moot point and a practice of futility. Watch this video again because I said
a lot of deep stuff that there's no way majority of folks can grasp in one watch because I didn't
come up with this in one thought. Support a real one.